sicksubmittertutorials.com 2013-05-17

# Privacy Policy

At **[www.sicksubmittertutorials.com](http://sicksubmittertutorials.com/)** , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by **[www.sicksubmittertutorials.com](http://sicksubmittertutorials.com/)** and how it is used. 

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, **[www.sicksubmittertutorials.com](http://sicksubmittertutorials.com/)** makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**   
**[www.sicksubmittertutorials.com](http://sicksubmittertutorials.com/)** does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**   
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on **[www.sicksubmittertutorials.com](http://sicksubmittertutorials.com/)**.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to **[www.sicksubmittertutorials.com](http://sicksubmittertutorials.com/)** and other sites on the Internet.   
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include;

  * Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on **[www.sicksubmittertutorials.com](http://sicksubmittertutorials.com/)** send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

**[www.sicksubmittertutorials.com](http://sicksubmittertutorials.com/)** has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. **[www.sicksubmittertutorials.com](http://sicksubmittertutorials.com/)** 's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do **not** sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

**Contacting Us**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us using the information below. 

admin [@] sicksubmittertutorials.com
